Guide to the Jay Haley Collection, 1957-2007 M1733
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 8. Media, 1969-2004
  - Subseries 8.4 Digital Video Discs, 1978-2004
    - Produced by Jay Haley and Madeleine Richeport-Haley. Jay Haley on Strategic Therapy, 1978, (50 min.); Remembering Milton H. Erickson, M.D. A Conversation with Jay Haley and John Weakland, 1980s, (59 min.); Milton H. Erickson, MD Explorer in Hypnosis and Therapy, 1993, (56 min.); Whither Family Therapy? A Jay Haley Version, 1997, (50 min.); The Guaranteed Cure. Of a Case of Bulimia/Anorexia, 1997, (53 min.); Remembering Gregory Bateson. A Conversation with Jay Haley and John Weakland, 1997, (78 min.); Approaching A Crisis. Threats of Violence, Divorce, and Suicide, 1997, (50 min.); Compulsory Therapy. A Case of Violence, 1999, (36 min.); Family Therapy at a Distance. A Case of Depression, 1999, (55 min.); Learning &Teaching Therapy with Jay Haley Series: A Positive Approach with a Psychotic Couple, 1999, (45 min.); Jay Haley on Directive Family Therapy, 1999, (40 min.); Brief Strategic therapy with Couples, 2001, (50 min.); How Many Clients are there in one Body?, 2001, (45 min.); Family Therapy in Bali, 2004, (28 min.) Additional Media Forthcoming., 1978-2004 (Box 55)
  - Subseries 8.5 Restricted Media (forthcoming)
    Access to Restricted Media
    The media in series 8.5 is restricted and will be available one hundred years from the date of creation.